

NGUYEN TRAN CONG DUY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER \$\ 079_8030_258

• DETAILS •

079_8030_258 duyng2512@gmail.com

Date of birth 25/12/1997

o SKILLS o

K8s and Service mesh

NoSQL(MongoDB, Redis)

Java (Spring, Vertex, Junit, Hibernate)

SQL (Oracle)

Message Queue (Kafka, RabbitMQ)

• LANGUAGES •

English

∘ HOBBIES ∘

Football, Marathon.

PROFILE

I am software developer with 2 years working in payment industry and 1 year in automotive industry. I have strong background in programming in Java, security, micro-service, best practice of designing API, scaling service in term of number of users and business change....

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Engineer at Openway Viet Nam

PERWAZ,

April 2020 — Present

Some notable project:

- 3-D Secure integrating with VISA and MasterCard: develop Restful service to handle 3-D authentication workflow, service achieve high throughput and high availability. Service is also highly configurable, able to allow or decline authentication base on business require Technology use: Web socket, K8S, Istio, Spring, Redis cache, MongoDB, Oracle DB...
- **Data migration for reconciliation**: using Debezium and Kafka to transfer data from online database to secondary database for supporting reconciliation.
- Integrate with NAPAS payment system: develop and test Restful and Host to Host (ISO 8583 message) to handle NAPAS various transaction type, (POS, ATM, E commerce, Billing, Top-up, ...) Technology use: Spring, jPOS, Java cryptography...
- **Health Monitoring:** central system for health monitoring. Technology use: Elasticsearch, Grafana, Prometheus., jmx, logback.

Software Engineer at Robert Bosch Engineering

BOSCH

April 2019 — April 2020

Working in billing team to improve billing workflow for client:

- Develop Restful, RPC interface in Spring framework, integrate with other service
- Develop Oracle procedure, function, views to support business requirement
- Deploy service on container and application server
- Perform unit testing, support user acceptance testing, support load testing, stress testing.

Software Intern at Robert Bosch Engineering

November 2018 — April 2019

- Develop internal tools in python, bash script to support manual task
- Resolve report Jira ticket
- Unit testing and document Restful API service

EDUCATION

Information Technology, Ho Chi Minh University of Technology and Education

June 2015 — April 2019

GPA: 8.2/10